ARPIT SRIVASTAVA

Game Developer and Designer

DETAILS

ADDRESS

Lucknow India

PHONE

+91-7518297283

EMAIL

arpitsrivstva@gmail.com

LINKS

Itch.io Profile

LinkedIn

<u>GitHub</u>

SKILLS

Unity Engine

C#

C++

Gimp

Adobe Fusion 360

IT Project Management

PROFILE

Built and working on 2D, 3D, WebGL, iOS, Android, Windows, Animation and Offline 2-player games. Designed Story mode, Board and Arcade games. I love ideating and making Prototypes as well. Currently having 1 year of experience.

Highly eager to play with my skills in a productive space around better people to improve and learn more.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Game Developer, Touchzing Media

Mumbai

Feb 2022 — Aug 2022

Creating samples and also creating mobile-based applications on Unity3D/2D with innovation and self ideation, while working through prototypes, prefabs, assets and animation.

Worked on #Slack for updates, planning and tracking.

Unity Developer, EventCombo

Jersey City

Sep 2022 - Jan 2023

Worked on a metaverse project and the ideation and designing with modelling samples.

Worked on #Jira for updates, planning and tracking.

EDUCATION

B.Tech., Ajeenkya D.Y. Patil University

Pune

Jun 2018 — Jun 2022

Graduated with High Honors.

LANGUAGES

Hindi
English
Russian
Japanese

HOBBIES

Ideating
Writing
Singing
Playing Brainy Games
Reading
Learning Languages.

MY NOTABLE PROJECTS

UnPop it! - A Board Game

WebGL. 2D.

(Genres: Soothing, Satisfying, Relaxing Board Game for two.)

Play it on any browser with this link:

https://arpitsrivstva.itch.io/unpop-it/

Pop/UnPop the bubbles and enjoy the relaxing game and calm down! A 2-player-game with the die roll.

Flappy Birdy Game

2D, PC.

(Used GameObject List, Lerp, ClampMagnitude, Renderer, Ceil, etc.)

Game's Website I built:

https://arpitsrivstva.github.io/Final-Year-Project-Flappy-Bird/

(Genres: Hypercasual, Arcade, Retro)

Collect points to maintain the brightness of your screen, thus the visibility in the game. Right click to pass through but not more than 5 Left clicks. My own ideated version of the cult game.

Apollo the 13th! - Game Script

Game Design.

(Genres: Fantasy, Sci-fi, Educational, Story, Survival, Simulation)

Document file and PPT:

https://github.com/arpitsrivstva/My-Apollo-13-Game-Design-Document-and-PPT

This is a **Game Designing** piece which I wrote on the classic movie – Apollo 13 (1995). The movie and project can be made into a big Story Mode Game and it could be a hit among the fans of the movie in an instant.

ACHIEVEMENTS

Top Final Year Project

University

My project was one of the Top Final Year Projects in the University in 2022. I led my team.

https://arpitsrivstva.github.io/Final-Year-Project-Flappy-Bird/

Best Prototype

Touchzing Media

My idea of a new game for the company which I represented to the head of my team through my prototype, was selected as the best prototype to be worked upon in future.